fameswap.com 2019-05-29

# Privacy

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use Fameswap.com ("Site"). By accessing or using this Site, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

#### Children Under the Age of 13

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Site. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features, make any purchases through the Site, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Site or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us.

#### Data Controler

The data controller for the information you provide or that is collected by Fameswap, LLC pursuant to this Privacy Policy is: Fameswap, LLC, 1601 Market Street Philadelphia PA 19103.

#### Short Version

At Fameswap we care about your privacy. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. We do not disclose it to others except as required to provide you with the services of the Fameswap.com website ("Site"), meaning - to allow you to buy, sell, share the information you want to share on the Site, pay for products, post reviews and so on.

We collect information that you provide us or voluntarily share with other users, and also some general technical information that is automatically gathered by our systems, such as IP address, browser information and cookies to enable you to have a better user experience and a more personalized browsing experience.

Information that you provide us in the process of the registration  will remain private and secure - including your contact information.

Information that you choose to publish  on the site (photos, videos, text, music, reviews, deliveries) - is no longer private, just like any information you publish online.

Technical information that is gathered by our systems , or third party systems, automatically may be used for Site operation, optimization, analytics, content promotion and enhancement of user experience. We may use your information to contact you - to provide notices related to your activities, or offer you promotions and general updates, but we will not let any other person, including sellers and buyers, contact you, other than through your user login.

The above are just the highlights. We encourage you to read more about information we collect, how we use it, understand what is the meaning of cookie (no, you can't eat it) and more in the long and boring version of our privacy policy below.

### Longer Version

Fameswap (including Fameswap LLC and its affiliates) respects your privacy and is committed to protect the personal information of its users - buyers, sellers, and visitors browsing the site ("Users" ). We believe that you have a right to know our practices regarding the information we may collect when you visit and/or use our website [https://fameswap.com ] (the "Site" ). This policy explains our privacy practices for the Site and services provided by Fameswap. By accessing and/or using the Site and its related sites, applications, services, goods and/or registering for a Fameswap account, you consent to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy, including to our collection, use, disclosure, processing and retention of your personal information. You can also learn how to limit sharing of information in this policy.

#### Information We Collect

When you register to the Site we ask you to provide certain personal information, including a valid email address, location and username. We may collect additional information such as physical address and additional authentication information, to provide you with the services you need (such as payment or withdrawal of funds, sending physical goods), or to ensure the marketplace integrity (for example, prevention of fraud). We collect information to provide better services and enhanced user experience to all of our Users.

In addition, we collect information while you access, browse, view or otherwise use the Site. In other words, when you access the Site we are aware of your usage of the Site, and may gather, collect and record the information relating to such usage, including geo-location information, IP address, device and connection information, browser information and web-log information, and all communications recorded by Users through the Site. We use that information to enhance user experience, personalize your browsing experience as well as monitor the Site for fraud and inappropriate content or behavior. We may also collect supplemental information obtained from third parties such as demographic and navigation data.

Additionally, in order to improve your online experience at Fameswap, we have implemented impression reporting. While you view our ads, we may gather user Global Unique Identifier, http request data like, user agent, ip, host, url, country/continent from which request made, browser info, device/operating system/operating system version.

Once you register, your username and additional information regarding your activity is made public and is visible to all Users of the Site. This information includes content you upload, your influencer channel description, campaign or business information, ratings, and any other additional information you may choose to add to your profile.

#### How do we collect Information?

You directly provide us with most of the information we collect. You do this by filling out the registration details on the Site, and by posting and sharing additional information voluntarily. This can include information about sellers and their Gigs, User's location, sharing of portfolio, ratings and feedbacks by buyers and anything you choose to add to your user profile. We also collect technical information indirectly and automatically through our systems. This information may include logging your Internet Protocol (IP) address, software configuration, operating system and use of cookies (cookies are small files sent from us to your computer and sometimes back). Cookies ultimately help us improve your navigation and ease of use of our Site. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. You can find further information about Cookies in this policy below, under cookies and Local Storage.

#### How do we use the Information collected?

We use personal information only as appropriate to provide you with quality service and security. For example, we may use the information collected from you to verify your identity. We may also use this information to establish and set up your account, verify or re-issue a password, log your activity and contact you from time to time. The information helps us improve our services to you, customize your browsing experience and inform you about additional products, services or promotions from Fameswap that may be of interest to you. In addition, this information helps us track any fraudulent activities and other inappropriate activities and monitor content integrity. Should you ever deactivate your account with us, we will keep your information on file, but only use it to comply with regulatory requirements and to contact you occasionally with the option to reactivate your account. We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those set out in this privacy policy. We process personal information on our servers in different jurisdictions world-wide. We may process your personal information on a server located outside the country in which you live.

We retain information as long as it is necessary and relevant for our operations. In addition, we may retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with the law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigation, enforce our Site terms and take other actions permitted by law.

#### Sharing Personal Information with Third Parties

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent.

We may combine your personal information with information we collect automatically or obtain from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services, content and advertising. If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us, you can opt-out through the link attached to each communication or by sending us an email.

We may provide your personal details to third parties, only in order to operate the Site, and prevent fraud and illegal activities, as detailed below:

#### Cookies and Local Storage

When you visit the Site, we may use industry-wide technologies such as "cookies" (or similar technologies), which store certain information on your computer and which will allow us, among other things, to enable automatic sign-in to the Site, make your browsing much more convenient and effortless and allow us to test user experience and offer you personalized browsing or promotions. Cookies (which may be html files, Flash files or other technology) are text files that help store user preferences and activity. The Site uses cookies to collect statistical data about its use, to tailor the Site's functionality to suit personal preferences and to assist with various aspects of Site operation. These files contain a variety of information such as information about webpages visited by you, the length of time you visited certain sites, data about how you came to visit particular sites, the scope and nature of those sites, areas viewed by you, and additional information.

#### Blocking Cookies

You may set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services, or to indicate when a cookie is being set by us. Information on deleting or controlling cookies is also available at [www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.aboutcookies.org/&sa=D&ust=1516849413266000&usg=AFQjCNEG6_SgTES10usaFxlPR18AodPLsw)  (note that this website is not provided by Fameswap, and we therefore cannot ensure its accuracy, completeness or availability). It is important to remember that many of our services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. For example, cookies may, in certain cases, save you from the need to enter usernames and passwords, and allow session continuity.

#### Retaining and Securing Your Information

We take appropriate security measures designed to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage, and processing practices, and introducing security measures, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to Fameswap employees, service providers and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations.

Of course, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. IN NO EVENT WILL FAMESWAP OR ITS SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES OR ANY PARTY INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING OR DELIVERING THE SITES BE LIABLE IN ANY MANNER WHATSOEVER FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF YOUR ACCESS, USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITES, OR IN CONNECTION WITH ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS OR LINE OR SYSTEM FAILURE (INCLUDING LOSS PROFITS, LOSS OF BUSINESS OR DATA, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, AND DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM INACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION OR INCONVENIENCE, DELAY, OR LOSS OF THE USE OF THE SITES). THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS APPLY WHETHER THE ALLEGED LIABILITY IS BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE STRICT LIABILITY OR ANY OTHER BASIS, EVEN IF IZEA OR ITS AFFILIATES OR ANY OTHER PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

The criteria used to determine our retention periods include:

The length of time we have an ongoing relationship with you and provide services to you (for example, for as long as you have an account with us or keep using the Sites)

Whether there is a legal obligation to which we are subject (for example, certain laws require us to keep records of your transactions for a certain period of time before we can delete them)

Whether retention is advisable considering our legal position (such as, for statutes of limitations, litigation or regulatory investigations)

#### Integrity of Your Data

Fameswap processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

#### Third Party Sites

While using the Site you may encounter links to third party websites. Fameswap is not responsible for these sites and has no responsibility or liability whatsoever with regard to privacy matters or any other legal matter with respect to such sites. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies and the terms of use or service of such websites. Our terms of use and our privacy policy apply only to information collected by us in accordance with this policy.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits California residents that are users of our Site to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send us an e-mail.

#### Your Canada Privacy Rights

We collect, use and disclose your personal information with your consent, which may be express or implied. You may withdraw your consent to the use and disclosure of your personal information by us or by third parties for marketing purposes at any time by contacting us as specified below under “Contact Us.” If you would like to access, update, or ask us to delete your preferences or the personal information that we have collected about you, please contact us, and we will respond to your request within 30 days.

#### Do Not Track Policy

Our Sites are not designed to respond to "do not track" signals received from browsers.

#### Use of Pixel Tags/Clear GIFs/Web Beacons

A pixel tag, also known as a clear GIF or web beacon, is an invisible tag placed on certain pages of our Sites but not on your computer. When you access these pages, pixel tags generate a generic notice of that visit. They usually work in conjunction with cookies, registering when a particular computer visits a particular page. If you turn off cookies, the pixel tag will simply detect an anonymous website visit.

#### Updating, Correcting, Removal/Opt-Out of Your Information

If your name, e-mail or postal address, telephone number or other personal information changes, you may update, correct or omit the relevant information by logging into our Site. You can also contact us by visiting our site and clicking “Contact Us.” If you prefer not to receive newsletters or other marketing e-mails from Fameswap, please let us know by clicking on the unsubscribe link within any newsletter or marketing e-mail you receive. Please be sure to include in any e-mail, your full name, e-mail address, postal address, and any message. Please note that such requests may take up to ten (10) days to become effective.

#### Your Choices about Your Personal Information

If you would like to review, correct, update, suppress, restrict or delete personal information that you have previously provided to us, or if you would like to receive an electronic copy of your personal information for purposes of transmitting it to another company (if this right to data portability is provided to you by law), you can contact us.

In your request, please make clear what personal information you would like to have changed, whether you would like to have your personal information suppressed from our database, or other limitations you would like to put on our use of your personal information. For your protection, we only fulfill requests for the personal information associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before fulfilling your request. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable.

Please note that we often need to retain certain data for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transaction that you began prior to requesting a change or deletion (e.g., when you make a purchase or enter a promotion, you may not be able to change or delete the personal information provided until after the completion of such purchase or promotion). Our databases and other records may have residual data which will not be removed. In addition, we also may not allow you to review certain data for legal, security or other reasons.

If at any time you believe that the Sites have not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please let us know. We will use good faith efforts to determine and correct the problem.

If you are an EEA resident, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a data protection authority about how we process your personal information.

#### Changes to the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, so please re-visit this page frequently.

Changes to this privacy policy are effective as of the stated "Last Update" and your continued use of the Site on or after the Last Update date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.

#### Corporate Change

In the event we go through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be among the assets transferred.
